Inventory of the Xin hua tong xun she (新华通讯社) radio broadcast transcripts
Hoover Institution Archives
Xin hua tong xun she (新华通讯社) radio broadcast transcripts
1948-1950
XX874
Hoover Institution Archives
5 manuscript boxes (2.1 linear feet)
Relates to the Chinese Civil War and to political and diplomatic developments in China.
Xin hua tong xun she.
Access
Collection is open for research.
The Hoover Institution Archives only allows access to copies of audiovisual items. To listen to sound recordings or to view videos or films during your visit, please contact the Archives at least two working days before your arrival. We will then advise you of the accessibility of the material you wish to see or hear. Please note that not all audiovisual material is immediately accessible.
Acquisition Information
Acquired by the Hoover Institution Archives.
Accruals
Materials may have been added to the collection since this finding aid was prepared. To determine if this has occurred, find the collection in Stanford University's online catalog at http://searchworks.stanford.edu/. Materials have been added to the collection if the number of boxes listed in the online catalog is larger than the number of boxes listed in this finding aid.
Historical Note
Chinese communist news agency.
Scope and Content of Collection
Relates to the Chinese Civil War and to political and diplomatic developments in China.
Radio broadcasting--China.; China--History--1949-1976.; China--History--Civil War, 1945-1949.
- 1948 February 15-28 (Box-folder 1: 1)
- 1948 June 2-26 (Box-folder 1: 2)
- 1948 July 1-30 (Box-folder 1: 3)
- 1948 August 1-18 (Box-folder 1: 4)
- 1948 August 19-30 (Box-folder 1: 5)
- 1948 September 1-30 (Box-folder 1: 6)
- 1948 October 1-15 (Box-folder 2: 1)
- 1948 October 16-31 (Box-folder 2: 2)
- 1948 November 1 (Box-folder 2: 3)
- 1948 November 2-21 (Box-folder 2: 4)
- 1949 April 5-28 (Box-folder 2: 5)
- 1949 May 1-11 (Box-folder 2: 6)
- 1949 May 14-31 (Box-folder 3: 1)
- 1949 June 1-19 (Box-folder 3: 2)
- 1949 June 20-30 (Box-folder 3: 3)
- 1949 July 3-31 (Box-folder 3: 4)
- 1949 August 1-16 (Box-folder 3: 5)
- 1949 August 17-31 (Box-folder 3: 6)
- 1949 September 1-25 (Box-folder 4: 1)
- 1949 September 26-28 (Box-folder 4: 2)
- 1949 October 1-20 (Box-folder 4: 3)
- 1949 October 21-31 (Box-folder 4: 4)
- 1949 November 1-15 (Box-folder 4: 5)
- 1949 November 16-30 (Box-folder 5: 1)
- 1949 December 1-11 (Box-folder 5: 2)
- 1949 December 12-24 (Box-folder 5: 3)
- 1949 December 25-31 (Box-folder 5: 4)
- 1950 August 16-December 25 (Box-folder 5: 5)